A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Art, Series C FA340
Rockefeller Archive Center
- NAR Artist Files, 1949-1979; 2; 17.6 Cubic Feet
  - Fontana, Lucio; Frankenthaler, Helen; Franklin, Ben (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Frantz, Sali; Frasconi, Antonio; Fredonia, SUNY College (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - G General (Box 10, Folder 86)
    Galerie Wolfgang Ketterer Gallery Masters Galeria Proteo Ganim, George Garrett, Stuart Garshanin, K. Gatch, L. Ghika, Nikos Hatzikyriakos Gates - Finn - Miro Gibson, Thomas Gilbert, Charles Gilbertson, Boris Glasco, J. Goeschl Gold Japanese Screen Gold, William Gramatopoulos Gray, Cleve Grebenak, Dorothy Green, Christopher Green, Gregory D. Greer, Manuel/Greer Gallery Gunther, Max Guston, Philip
  - Gabino, Amadeo (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Gabo, Naum; Galaxy-Kiesler; Gambling, William; Genesco, SUNY College; Genis, Rene (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Gabo, Naum; Galaxy-Kiesler; Gambling, William; Genesco, SUNY College; Genis, Rene (Box 10, Folder 0088A)
  - Germinal (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Germinal (Box 10, Folder 0089A)
  - Giacometti, Alberto and Diego (lamps) (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Giacometti, Alberto (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Giloli, Emile (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Glarner, Fritz (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Glarner, Fritz (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Glass; Gleizes, Albert; Gonzalez, Julio; Goodnough, Robert; Gorky, Arshile; Gottlieb, Adolph (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Grausman, Philip; Graves, Morris; Greek art; Greenbaum, Dorothea; Greenly, Colin; Grief, Harriet; Grigorian, Marcos; Grilley, Robert; Grilo, Sarah (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Grausman, Philip; Graves, Morris; Greek art; Greenbaum, Dorothea; Greenly, Colin; Grief, Harriet; Grigorian, Marcos; Grilley, Robert; Grilo, Sarah (Box 11, Folder 0096A)
  - Gris, Juan (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Gris, Juan (Box 11, Folder 0097A)
  - Gris, Juan (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Gris, Juan (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Gross, Chaim; Guarducci, Otello; Guayasamin, Oswaldo; Guastella, Nick; Guglielmi, O. Louis; Guttuso, Renato; Guys, Constanin (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - H General (Box 11, Folder 101)
    Haacke, Hans Haas, Helen Haas, Richard Haass, Terry Hadengue, Sebastien Haese Haku Maki Halpert, Edith Gregor Hamada Shosi Hament Hanspers Harnett, William Hartert Hartung, Hans Hatfield, Honorable Mark O. Hayes, David Hayer, Tarantella Heeramenck, Nasli Held, Al Helion, Jean Henry, E.L. Herrera Herter, Adele Hexdenryrs Hnizdovsky, Jacques Hawley, Helen Holt Habbah Hogarth, P Hoppner, John Horses Hosiasson, P. Hugo, Breton Hunt, Richard Hyde, Scott
  - H General (Box 11, Folder 0101A)
    Harris, E. Himme, Alice Hodges, Frances
  - Habbah, Abraham; Hague, Raoul; Haitian Paintings; Hajdu, Etienne; Hamblett, Theora (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Harpur College; Hart, George "Pop" (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Hartigan, Grace; Hartley, Marsden; Hauswedell, Ernst; Hawkins, Peter (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Hayes, David V. (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Hayes, David V. (Box 12, Folder 0105A)
  - Hayes, David V. (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Hayes, David V. (Box 12, Folder 0106A)
  - Heise, William; Hepworth, Barbara; Higgins, Edward; Hirsch, Stefan (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Heise, William; Hepworth, Barbara; Higgins, Edward; Hirsch, Stefan (Box 12, Folder 0107A)
  - Hokanson, Hans; Holden, Norma; Holst, Beate Wheeler; Honegger, Gottfried; Horwitt, Will (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Hudson River Museum; Hughes, Burton; Hull, John; Hurtado, A. (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - I General (Box 13, Folder 110)
    IGAS Ihle, John Ihlenfeld Ikayukta Impressionist Project India Indian Inst. of Cont. Arts Item
  - I General (Box 13, Folder 0110A)
    Ingraham, Hollis S.
  - Indiana, Robert; Inness, George; Instituto Historico e Geografico Brasileiro (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Indiana, Robert; Inness, George; Instituto Historico e Geografico Brasileiro (Box 13, Folder 0111A)
  - Inventory lists (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Inventory lists (Box 13, Folder 0112A)
  - Inventory lists (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Inventory lists (Box 13, Folder 0113A)
  - Ipousteguy, Jean (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Ipousteguy, Jean (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Geoffrey, Iqbal (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Iranian artists; Isobe, Yukihisa (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - J General (Box 14, Folder 118)
    Jackson, I. Jade Brooches Jaeckel, Willi Janis, Sidney Gallery Joseph, Jasmin Jamec, Andrej Jensen, Alfred Jessica Joe, James C. Johnson, Arthur C. Johnson, Gerald Johnston Jones, Sally Juste, Joseph Louis
  - Japanese; Jawlensky, Alexei; Jeio; Johns, Jasper; Jones, Frederic (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - K General (Box 14, Folder 120)
    Kalaitzidou Kampmann Kaplan, Saul Mrs. Karoly, F. Kawashima Keck, Sheldon and Caroline Keck Reports on Klee Kee Leemeeoomee Kenojuak Kemeny Keppel, David Ketten, Maurice Keystone Blue Paper Company Khalil, Mohammed Omer Kierzkowski Kikuhata, Mohuma Kimball, Edward J. Kilstrom Kimura, S. Kuchner, Ernst Ludwig King, William D. Kingmeata Kitaoka, Fumio Kitas, R.B. Kleinbardt, Ruth Kline, F. Klipstein Knipschild, R. Keonig Galerie Wolfgang Ketterer Konsad Koni, Nicholaus Koshiba, H.T. Koud Kramer, Mr. and Mrs. Milton Lurie Kraushaar Gallery Kunststil (book) Kurzern, Aaron
  - Kalinowski, Horst Ego; Kandinsky, Wassily; Katayama, Toshi; Kelly, Ellsworth; Kettle, Tilly (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Kiesler, Frederick; King, William; Kirstein, Lincoln (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Kivijarvi, Harry; Kiyonobu, Torii (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Klee, Paul (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Klee, Paul (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Klee, Paul (Box 14, Folder 0125A)
  - Kline, Alama; Kobashi, Yasuhide (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Kline, Alama; Kobashi, Yasuhide (Box 14, Folder 0126A)
  - Kobzdej, Alexander; Koenig, Fritz; Kohn, Gabe (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Kolar, Jiri (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Kolbe, Georg (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - Korean vases; Kornbrust, Leo; Kornfeld, E.W. & Klipstein (Dealer); Krasinski, Edward; Krause, Glen; Kruger, Louise; Kuh, Katherine; Kuniyoshi, Yasuo (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - L General (Box 15, Folder 131)
    La Croix, Richard La Fresnaye, Roger de Lalanne Lamp Mounting Lamps Langlais, Bernard Lapicque Lapinski, Thadeus Latin American Artists Laurens, Henri Lawrence, J. Lead Eagles Leather Leather Preservative (for Kalinowski) Lee, Caroline Leighton's (Fred Leighton Company) Lettering Levine, Jack The Lighthouse Queens Center Lincoln Warehouse Lindner, Richard Lippencott Co. Little, Lisa Litto, Frank Loan Loan Schedule Loeb, Albert Lorne, Naomi Lourve Lubic, Milan Lucy (Eskimo Art)
  - Lachaise, Gaston (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Lachaise, Gaston (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Lachaise, Gaston (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Lachaise, Gaston (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - Lam, Wilfredo; Lassaw, Ibram (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - Lam, Wilfredo; Lassaw, Ibram (Box 16, Folder 0136A)
  - Laurent, Robert; Lavaggi, Rene; Leger, Fernand (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - Laurent, Robert; Lavaggi, Rene; Leger, Fernand (Box 16, Folder 0137A)
  - Lehmbruck, Wilhelm (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Leone, Mauro (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - Liberman, Alexander (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - Liberman, Sandu; Lieberman, William S.; Lichtenstein, Roy (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - Liberman, Sandu; Lieberman, William S.; Lichtenstein, Roy (Box 16, Folder 0141A)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques (Box 16, Folder 143)
  - Lippold, Richard; Lipton, Seymour; Louis, Morris; Lowe, Maxine; Lux-Feininger, Theodore; Lytle, Richard (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Lippold, Richard; Lipton, Seymour; Louis, Morris; Lowe, Maxine; Lux-Feininger, Theodore; Lytle, Richard (Box 17, Folder 0144A)
  - M General (Box 17, Folder 145)
    MacDonald, John MacIver Mack Magnelli, Alberto Maine Maiorana, Ronald Majewsky, Lawrence J. Mallory, Ronald Malone, Robert Mantegna Marsegha Marsh Martin, Aldemar Masaccio Masoherini Masorovsky Masson, Andre Matare, Ewald Mavromichalis, Chryssa "Maya Stela" MacCausland Mediterranean Iran Amlack Meekev, D.J. Meigs, Kelley Meredith, John Micassi Miki, Tomio Milinan Millares, Manolo Mills, R. Minami Gall Minn, E. Minor Minquzzi Miscellaneous Artists Mitchell, La Verne Modigliani, Amedeo Mohassess, Bohman Monroe, Keith Moon Rock Moda Morales, Armando Mosca, Ivan Moses, Gina Munakata Murals Murals - Installation Murphy, Catherine Murphy, Ed
  - Mabiel; Machlin, Sheldon; Macri, Guiseppe; Magritte (Box 17, Folder 146)
  - Maillol, Aristede (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - Maillol, Aristede (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Maillol, Aristede (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - Mallary, Robert; Mallo, Maruja; Maloney, Daniel; Marble; Marca-Relli, Conrad (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - March, Esteban; Marcks, Gerhard; Marini, Marino (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - March, Esteban; Marcks, Gerhard; Marini, Marino (Box 17, Folder 0151A)
  - Marisol; Marlborough (Gallery); Marymount College; Mastroianni, Umberto (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - Marisol; Marlborough (Gallery); Marymount College; Mastroianni, Umberto (Box 18, Folder 0152A)
  - Mathieu, Georges (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 154)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 0154A)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 155)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 156)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 157)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 158)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 159)
  - Matisse, Henri (Box 18, Folder 0159A)
  - Matute, Miquel; Maurer, Alfred; Meadmore, Clement (Box 18, Folder 160)
  - Meredith, Burgess; Merkel, O.; Metropolitan Museum of Art; Mexican art (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - Meredith, Burgess; Merkel, O.; Metropolitan Museum of Art; Mexican art (Box 19, Folder 0161A)
  - Miller, Richard; Millman, Edward; Mirko, Basaldella (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - Miro, Joan (Box 19, Folder 163)
  - Miro, Joan (Box 19, Folder 164)
  - Miro, Joan (Box 19, Folder 165)
  - Modern (various artists); Modigliani, Amedeo; Molas; Moldenhawer, Aina; MoMA (Museum of Modern Art); Mondrian, Piet (Box 19, Folder 166)
  - Modern (various artists); Modigliani, Amedeo; Molas; Moldenhawer, Aina; MoMA (Museum of Modern Art); Mondrian, Piet (Box 19, Folder 0166A)
  - Montenegro, Roberto (Box 19, Folder 167)
  - Montenegro, Roberto (Box 19, Folder 0167A)
  - Moore, Henry (Box 19, Folder 168)
  - Moore, Henry (Box 19, Folder 169)
  - Moore, Henry (Box 19, Folder 170)
  - Moore, Henry (Box 19, Folder 0170A)
  - Moore, Henry (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - Morandi, Giorgio; Morg'io; Morgan, Norma; Morris, Robert; Moshaty, Shaheen (Box 20, Folder 172)
  - Motherwell, Robert (Box 20, Folder 173)
  - Motherwell, Robert (Box 20, Folder 174)
  - Mousia; Moy, Seong; Muccini, Marcello; Multiwax; Munch, Edward; Mundt, Michael (Box 20, Folder 175)
  - Munter, Gabrielle (Box 20, Folder 176)
  - N General (Box 20, Folder 177)
    Nadworny, Arnold M. Nagler, Fred Nakian Nakurridjilmi, Jimmy Name-plates, Picture-Memorial Gift Namuli, Rosemary Native Paintings New Talent New York Botanical Garden Society Tour New York University Nicholson, Ben Noon, John A. Nyoaard, K.K.
  - Nadelman, Elie (Box 20, Folder 178)
  - Nadelman, Elie (Box 20, Folder 179)
  - Nagare, Masayuki (Box 20, Folder 180)
  - Navigo; Negret, Edgar (Box 21, Folder 181)
  - Nevelson, Louise (Box 21, Folder 182)
  - Nevelson, Louise (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - New Decade; Newman; New York City Community College; Nichols, John C.; Nigerian art; Ninth Assembly District Republican Club (Box 21, Folder 184)
  - Noguchi, Isamu (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Noguchi, Isamu; Ntiro, Sam J. (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - O General (Box 21, Folder 187)
    Obelisk Water Proofing Obin, Philome Old Print Shop of Westchester Oldenburg Geometric House Olds, Elizabeth Omari, Mwariko A. Onosato, Toshinobu Oppenheim Ouchi, Kuni Ozenfant, Amedei Owls, Juni Indian
  - Obragon, Alajandro; Ocampo, Miguel; Okada, Kenzo; Okollo, Jean; Oneonta, SUNY College (Box 21, Folder 188)
  - Oriental art (Box 22, Folder 189)
  - Oriental art (Box 22, Folder 0189A)
  - Oriental art (Box 22, Folder 190)
  - Oriental art (Box 22, Folder 0190A)
  - Oriental art (Box 22, Folder 191)
  - Orion, Ezra; Ortuzar, Mariano (Box 22, Folder 192)
  - P General (Box 22, Folder 193)
    Paalen, Wolfgang Packing Pagliacci Paine, Frances Pan American Union Palazzo, Salvador Paolozzi, A.R. Paris Auction Parke-Bernet Galleries Parma Gallery Partington, Susan T. Pascal-Sculptress Pascin Patterson, Guy Paz, Octavio Perelman, Luis Perls Gallery Phelps Philadelphia Museum of Art Photographer, Albany, E.M. Weil Photographs-Condition-Art Photographs Picture Lights Pierce, Leona Piene, Nan Plaques Plate, Walter Playhouse Pleasants, Frederick R. Plexiglass in small quantities Pocker (receipt) Poesies of Mallarme (book) Poland Picture Hangers Polish Artists Pool bases Porcelain Enamelling Porter, Lillian Probst, Joachim Public Education Association Pudlo Purchases, Possible Miscellaneous Pugh, T.
  - P General (Box 22, Folder 0193A)
  - Pauley, Hal; Peale; Pearson, Henry; Persian Frames; Peruvian art; Peterdi, Gabor; Peto, John F. (Box 22, Folder 194)
  - Pauley, Hal; Peale; Pearson, Henry; Persian Frames; Peruvian art; Peterdi, Gabor; Peto, John F. (Box 22, Folder 0194A)
  - Phillips, David (Box 22, Folder 195)
  - Picasso, Pablo
    - General (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - General (Box 23, Folder 0196A)
    - General (Box 23, Folder 197)
    - General (Box 23, Folder 0197A)
    - General (Box 23, Folder 198)
    - A-D (Box 23, Folder 199)
    - A-D (Box 23, Folder 0199A)
    - E-G (Box 23, Folder 200)
    - E-G (Box 23, Folder 0200A)
    - H-K (Box 23, Folder 201)
    - L-N (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - O-R (Box 24, Folder 203)
    - O-R (Box 24, Folder 0203A)
    - S (Box 24, Folder 204)
    - T (Box 24, Folder 205)
    - T (Box 24, Folder 0205A)
    - U-W (Box 24, Folder 206)
    - "The Bathers" (Box 24, Folder 207)
    - "The Bathers" (Box 24, Folder 208)
    - "Girl with Mandolin" (Box 24, Folder 209)
    - "Girl with Mandolin" (Box 24, Folder 210)
    - "Girl with Mandolin" (Box 24, Folder 211)
    - Graphics (Box 25, Folder 212)
    - Graphics (Box 25, Folder 0212A)
    - "La Guitare" (Box 25, Folder 213)
    - "Interior with Girl Drawing" (Box 25, Folder 214)
    - "Interior with Girl Drawing" (Box 25, Folder 214.1)
    - "Les Moissoneurs (Harvesters)" (Box 25, Folder 215)
    - "Nymphs and Fauns" (Box 25, Folder 216)
    - "Pitcher and Bowl of Fruit" (Box 25, Folder 217)
    - Stein Collection (Box 25, Folder 218)
    - Stein Collection (Box 25, Folder 0218A)
    - Stein Collection (Box 25, Folder 219)
    - Stein Collection (Box 25, Folder 0219A)
    - Stein Collection (Box 25, Folder 220)
    - Stein Collection (Box 25, Folder 0220A)
    - Stein Collection (photo album/scrapbook) (Box 26, Folder 221)
    - Stein Collection (photo album/scrapbook) (Box 26, Folder 0221A)
    - "Woman with Striped Bodice" (Box 26, Folder 222)
    - "Woman with Striped Bodice" (Box 26, Folder 223)
    - "Woman with Striped Bodice" (Box 26, Folder 224)
    - Prints (Box 26, Folder 225)
    - Tapestries
      - General (Box 27, Folder 226)
      - General (Box 27, Folder 0226A)
      - A-F (Box 27, Folder 227)
        General note
        Reviewed and opened by AF, 10/07/2004.
      - A-F (Box 27, Folder 0227A)
      - G (Box 27, Folder 228)
      - H-K (Box 27, Folder 229)
      - L-O (Box 27, Folder 230)
      - P (Box 27, Folder 231)
      - S-T (Box 27, Folder 232)
      - Authentication, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 233)
      - "Dejeuner sur L'Herbe" (Box 27, Folder 234)
      - "Girl with Toy Boat" (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - "Girl with Toy Boat" (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - "Girl with Toy Boat" (Box 28, Folder 0236A)
      - "La Guernica" (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - "La Guernica" (Box 28, Folder 238)
      - "La Guernica" (Box 28, Folder 239)
      - Lehman College Exhibit, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 240)
      - Loan to Everson Museum, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 241)
  - Pignon, Edouard (Box 28, Folder 242)
  - Plateria, Ortega; Pol Mara; Polesello, Rogelio; Poleskie, Steve (Box 28, Folder 243)
  - Pollock, Jackson (Box 28, Folder 244)
  - Pomodoro, Arnaldo (Box 29, Folder 245)
  - Pomodoro, Gio (Box 29, Folder 246)
  - Pomodoro, Gio (Box 29, Folder 247)
  - Portinari, Candido; Post, Charles J.; Pots, Earthenware (Box 29, Folder 248)
  - Portinari, Candido; Post, Charles J.; Pots, Earthenware (Box 29, Folder 0248A)
  - Prendergast Library; Priest, Allan (Box 29, Folder 249)
  - Primitive art masterpieces (Box 29, Folder 250)
  - Prints; Prison art (Box 29, Folder 251)
  - R General (Box 29, Folder 252)
    Racks and bookshelves Raible, Alton Rail Road Express Rasmussen, Anne-Marie Raumbug, Gabino Rauschenberg, Robert Red, Green and Yellow by Riopelle Redon, J.J. Reilly Rockland County Renoir Renzi Reproductions Republican Rockland County Return of the Warburgh Reynal, Jeanne Richier, Germaine Richterich Rights and Reproductions Ringling Museum Rivera, Manuel Rizzoli Robinson, Gladys Lloyd Robles Rebozo Rocchi, Gualberto Rodriguez-Lorrain Rodriguez, Marcelino Romano, Claire F. D. Roosevelt Portrait Rosenquist, James Rosenthal Ross, Edward Rothko Rousseau, Henry Rubenstein, Louis W. Runacher
  - R General (Box 29, Folder 0252A)
    Racks and bookshelves Raible, Alton Rail Road Express Rasmussen, Anne-Marie Raumbug, Gabino Rauschenberg, Robert Red, Green and Yellow by Riopelle Redon J.J. Reilly Rockland County Renoir Renzi Reproductions Republican Rockland County, J.J. Reilly Restorers and Restoration Return of the Warburgh Reynal, Jeanne Richier, Germaine Richterich Rights and Reproductions Ringling Museum Rivera, Manuel Rizzoli Robinson, Gladys Lloyd Robles Rebozo Rocchi, Gualberto Rodriguez-Lorrain Rodriguez, Marcelino Romano, Claire FDR Portrait Rosenquist, James Rosenthal Ross, Edward Rothko Rousseau, Henry Rubenstein, Louis W. Runacher
  - Rafael, Valdivia; Ramirez, Eduardo; Raveau, Marcel; Reder, Bernard (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - Reese, S.W. & Co.; Reinhoud, Nono; Reiter, Candace; Reveron, Armando (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - Richards, John (Box 30, Folder 255)
  - Richards, John (Box 30, Folder 256)
  - Richardson, Sam (Box 30, Folder 257)
  - Rickey, George (Box 30, Folder 258)
  - Rickey, George (Box 30, Folder 259)
  - Riopelle, Jean-Paul; Rivera, Diego; Roberts, William; Rockefeller, Michael (Box 30, Folder 260)
  - Rodin, Auguste; Ronald, William; Rosai, Ottone (Box 30, Folder 261)
  - Rodin, Auguste; Ronald, William; Rosai, Ottone (Box 30, Folder 0261A)
  - Rosati, James (Box 30, Folder 262)
  - Rostand, Michel (Box 30, Folder 263)
  - Roualt, Georges (Box 30, Folder 264)
  - Ruiz, Matute; Ruthen, John; Ruzicka, Wilhelm (Box 30, Folder 265)
  - Ruiz, Matute; Ruthen, John; Ruzicka, Wilhelm (Box 30, Folder 0265A)
  - Sa-Sh General (Box 31, Folder 266)
    Sacilotto Saetto Saff, Donald Sa'idi Sailboat Painting Saito, Kiyoshi Sales Okada Salles, George Salome Salmony, Alfred Sam, Bal Krishna Sander, Ludwig Sandoval, Corliss Santomaso, G. Sargent, John Singer Satterthwaite, John D. Savelli, Angelo Scanlon Scarab Schanker, Louis Scheinman, Ester Schenck Schepis, Angelo Schina, Mary Schmidt, K. Schrag, Karl Scranton Sculptors-Head of JDR, Jr. Schreffer Microtemps Segy Primitives Sekine, Yoshio Seligmann Sepehri, Sorab Serpan Service Elevator Seymour Sheeler, Charles Shepley Sheple, P. Shermer, W.M. Shirae, Shiro Ship Painting Shipping Shockler, H.
  - Sa-Sh General (Box 31, Folder 0266A)
    Senegalese Girl Signac, Paul Seto, Jesus
  - Si-Sm General (Box 31, Folder 267)
    Sickert Signs Sills, Joyce Silver Simpliciano, Alla Siquireros, David Alfaro Sister Bianca Sister Mary Corita Skaggs, Robert Lee Slides Sliding door Smart, Wini Smiley, Helen Peto Smith, Xanthus
  - Si-Sm General (Box 31, Folder 0267A)
    Smith, Carl
  - So-Sv General (Box 31, Folder 268)
    Sobert Soloman Sonenberg, Jack Soria, Salvador Sowers, R. Spanish Art Spanish Painting Spanish Pavilion World's Fair Spear, Athena T. Staempfli Stark Steig Stevenson, James Stolen, Oddbjorn Stone Stuart, Gilbert Sugai, Kumi Summers Sutherland, Graham V. Suttman Sviglas, Philip
  - Salisbury, Frank O.; Sani, Alberto; Scarfe, Gerald; Scheibe, Fred (Box 31, Folder 269)
  - Schoffer, Nicolas; Schuler, Melvin; Schulz, Hans W.; Schwitters, Kurt; Scipione; Screens (Box 31, Folder 270)
  - Schoffer, Nicolas; Schuler, Melvin; Schulz, Hans W.; Schwitters, Kurt; Scipione; Screens (Box 31, Folder 0270A)
  - Sculptures; Segal, George (Box 31, Folder 271)
  - Seley, Jason; Seliger, Charles (Box 31, Folder 272)
  - Shahn, Ben; Shaw, Ernest; Sheridan, John; Shinoda; Shivitz, Barbara (Box 31, Folder 273)
  - Shahn, Ben; Shaw, Ernest; Sheridan, John; Shinoda; Shivitz, Barbara (Box 31, Folder 0273A)
  - Shuter, M.; Signae, Paul; Sivers, Kent; Skidmore College (Box 32, Folder 274)
  - Shuter, M.; Signae, Paul; Sivers, Kent; Skidmore College (Box 32, Folder 0274A)
  - Smith, David (Box 32, Folder 275)
  - Smith, David (Box 32, Folder 276)
  - Smith, David (Box 32, Folder 0276A)
  - Smith, David (Box 32, Folder 277)
  - Smith, Tony (Box 32, Folder 278)
  - Smith, Tony (Box 32, Folder 279)
  - Snelson, Kenneth (Box 32, Folder 280)
  - Somaini, Frencesco; Soto, Jesus; Soulages, Pierre; South American art; Soyer, Raphael (Box 32, Folder 281)
  - Somaini, Frencesco; Soto, Jesus; Soulages, Pierre; South American art; Soyer, Raphael (Box 32, Folder 0281A)
  - Spencer, Niles (Box 33, Folder 282)
  - Stahly, Francois (Box 33, Folder 283)
  - Stahly, Francois (Box 33, Folder 284)
  - Stahly, Francois (Box 33, Folder 285)
  - Stahly, Francois (Box 33, Folder 286)
  - Stamos; Stankiewicz, Richard; Stanley, Gordon; Stearns, Junis B.; Steig, William; Stein, Gertrude (Box 33, Folder 287)
  - Stella, Frank; Sully, Thomas; Suzuki, James; Szyszlo, Fernando de (Box 33, Folder 288)
  - Stella, Frank; Sully, Thomas; Suzuki, James; Szyszlo, Fernando de (Box 33, Folder 0288A)
  - T General (Box 33, Folder 289)
    Taeuber-Arp, Sopie H. Takeda Talbot Triad Tamayo, Rufino Tappan, Diana Tapestries Tawney, Lenore Tchelichew, Pavel Thomas, Jerome J. Tidwell Tinguely, Jean Tamaszewski, Lubomir Tomioko, Soichiro Toneyama, K. Tooker, George Torres-Garcia, Joaquin Tours Tovgy Trozzi Turcios Twombly, Cy Tyabji
  - T General (Box 33, Folder 0289A)
    Thomas, A.P. Rochelle
  - Tables (Box 33, Folder 290)
  - Tajiri, Shinkichi (Box 33, Folder 291)
  - Tajiri, Shinkichi (Box 33, Folder 292)
  - Takis; Tarbox, Christine; Tate, Nairne; Tautze, Willy (Box 33, Folder 293)
  - Taylor, Wendy; Temple Israel; Teruz, Orlando; Thornton, Leslie; Time-Life (Box 33, Folder 294)
  - Tobey, Mark (Box 34, Folder 295)
  - Tobey, Mark (Box 34, Folder 0295A)
  - Tomlin, Bradley Walker (Box 34, Folder 296)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 297)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 298)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 299)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 300)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 301)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 0301A)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 302)
  - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri (Box 34, Folder 303)
  - Town, Harold; Townley, Hugh R.; Trova, Ernest; Tusnelda (Box 34, Folder 304)
  - Town, Harold; Townley, Hugh R.; Trova, Ernest; Tusnelda (Box 34, Folder 0304A)
  - U General (Box 35, Folder 305)
    Uht, John Uht, Charles F. Uchima Union Steel Products, Co. Upton, Richard Unwin, Nora S. Use Fork New York, Idaho Up
  - Uecker, Gunther; Union Church; Unknown; Utamaro, Kitagawa; Utica (Box 35, Folder 306)
  - Uecker, Gunther; Union Church; Unknown; Utamaro, Kitagawa; Utica (Box 35, Folder 0306A)
  - V General (Box 35, Folder 307)
    Van Doesburg Verve Vickrey, R. Vietnamese Painting Viteri, Oswaldo Vivancos, Miguel Garcia Vlaminck Volk Volikmer, J. Vollmer Von Bothmer, Dietrich Vuillard Vuilliamy, Justin Edward
  - V General (Box 35, Folder 0307A)
    Van Dresser, William
  - Valentin, Curt; Valtat (Box 35, Folder 308)
  - Valentin, Curt; Valtat (Box 35, Folder 0308A)
  - Vanderlyn, Henry (Box 35, Folder 309)
  - Vanderlyn, Henry (Box 35, Folder 310)
  - Vanderlyn, Henry (Box 35, Folder 311)
  - Van Dongen, Kees (Box 35, Folder 312)
  - Van Gogh, Vincent (Box 35, Folder 313)
  - Vasarely, Victor (Box 35, Folder 314)